I’ve gotten the feeling everything was set in motion
扉を開けたあの瞬間から
the moment I opened that door
全てが動き出した気がしてた
My zero-gravity teenage days have been ticking away
息つく暇もなく走りぬけて
I race through them without even the time to catch my breath
刻んできた  無重力十代デイズ
They say that’s “just like Cinderella”, but
「まるでシンデレラ」なんて言うけど
a flower doesn’t bloom in a day, does it?
花は一日にして咲かずでしょ?
Even though I sigh for full-fledged adulthood
いっちょまえに溜息をついても
I’ve still got plenty of growing up to do
まだまだオトナになれない
We’ve always been able to share a “sibling” type of closeness
姉妹(きょうだい)のような距離で居れるから
so even if I whine, you also dote on me
弱音も吐けば  甘えもするのよ
It’s only when you scold my good-for-nothing self
ぐーたらなワタシ叱る時だけ
that you suddenly become serious
急に本気になる
I wanna laugh together with you in both ups and downs
山のときも谷のときも  君と笑っていたい
Do you understand that muddled statement? I want to tell you anyway
言葉足らず  ご存知でしょ?  それでも伝えたい
I’ll pack my feelings towards you,
君への想い
the depths of my heart,
思いの丈  詰め込んだ
into my singing voice and make it ring out with a boom
歌声バクオンで響かせて
May it reach you
君へ届け
I’m looking up at the first star in the sky
一番星  見上げてる
beyond the orange-clouded evening sky
夕空  オレンジの雲越えて
I know you’re more straightforward than anyone,
誰よりも真っ直ぐな  君知ってるから
so listen up well, okay, I’m giving you my all-time highest
ちゃんと聞いていてね  ワタシ史上最高の
THANK YOU!
アリガト!
Being too reckless is just right
無鉄砲なくらいが丁度いいなんて
I try out various things, but
色々試してみるけど
when I stretch myself too far
つま先立ちで背伸びをしたって
I grow numb and start stumbling right away
すぐにシビれてよろけちゃう
I feel it each time I look at the hallway mirror
廊下の鏡見るたび感じてる
“What’s unique about me?”
「自分らしさはドコにあるんだろ？」
I ask frustratedly and you
テンパる私を優しく撫でた
give me a gentle pat on the head
君に問いかける
Rain or shine, I don’t want to leave any regrets
晴れのときも雨のときも  後悔はしたくない
No one else has ever given me the courage to keep going that you have
進む勇気くれてるのは  他の誰でもない
May it reach you
君へ届け
Face forward with all your body and soul,
その瞳を輝かせ
eyes shining bright
全身全霊で前向いて
Let it ring out to you
君に響け
under this sky that connects us,
つながっている空の下
my heart with its beat that beats in time with yours
同じビート刻む  このハート
I’ll dedicate this to you, the biggest crybaby of them all
誰よりも泣き虫な  君に捧げよう
It’s a feeling that I’ve always kept hidden...my all-time highest
ずっと隠してた  ワタシ史上最高の
THANK YOU!
アリガト!
May it reach you
君に届け
Let me take your spilled tears
こぼれ落ちたその涙
and wrap you and them up in a fluffy towel
ふわふわのタオルで包ませて
May it reach you
君へ届け
I’m looking up at the first star in the sky
一番星  見上げてる
beyond the orange-clouded evening sky
夕空　オレンジの雲越えて
I know you’re more straightforward than anyone,
誰よりも真っ直ぐな  君知ってるから
so listen up well, okay, I’m giving you my all-time highest
ちゃんと聞いていてね  ワタシ史上最高の
THANK YOU!
アリガト!